https://www.gilmanprecision.com/privacy-policy/

SpindlesBelt Driven SpindlesMotorized SpindlesInTronix SpindleSlidesDovetail SlidesHardened Box Way SlidesLinear Guide SlidesManual & Motorized XY StagesRepair ServicesMachine Slide RepairCNC Spindle RepairCustomizationMachine ModulesResourcesProduct ConfiguratorProduct CatalogsIdea BulletinsISO CertificateVideo GalleryOur FacilityNewsRep LocatorContact Us Privacy PolicyGilman Precision Values Your PrivacyWe have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. We do not sell, rent, loan, or give your email address or other personal information to anybody and will never do so.How We At Gilman Precision Protect Your PrivacyThe information we collect is used to improve the content of our web page, used to customise the content and/or layout of each page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our GilmanPrecision.com website.Sharing & UsageWe may collect the domain name and email address (where possible) of visitors to our GilmanPrecision.com Web site. The email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, the email addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, fax number.Use Of Web TrackingWhen we send you emails, we may include a web beacon to allow us to determine the number of people who open our emails, our GilmanPrecision.com Web site. When you click on a link in an email, we may record this individual response to allow us to customise our offerings to you. Web tracking may collect only limited information, such as a cookie identifier, time and date of a page being viewed, and a description of the page on which the web tracking resides (the URL).LinksThe GilmanPrecision.com website contains links to other sites. Gilman Precision is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. We recommend users read the privacy statements of each linked website.Correction/Updating Personal InformationIf a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct or update that user’s personal data provided to us. At any time, customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by contacting us.Why Did You Receive A Mailing From Gilman Precision?Our outbound email marketing is permission based. If you received a mailing from us, our records indicate that your name was collected contact information that we received (a) from you, (b) a representative of your company or organisation, (c) a mutual association we may have in common, or (d) you have expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (”opt-in”), or (e) you have registered to have a relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.How Can You Stop Receiving Email From Gilman Precision?Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to stop receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the unsubscribe or update profile links at the end of any email.Privacy Policy DateThis policy was updated on April 2018.
Have A Question?
Contact UsPlease fill out the form below & we will contact you in a timely fashion.Full Name
First
Last Email Address Company NamePhone Number*Message
Get In TouchFacebookLinkedInYouTube
